If you remember back to the final app that we're building,
如果还记得我们将构建的最终应用的话
there are five metrics that we're going to be tracking.
就会发现我们将跟踪五个指标
Running, biking, swimming, sleeping, and eating.
跑步 骑行 游泳 睡眠和饮食
So what we're going to do is inside of our helpers.js file,
我们将打开 helpers.js 文件
let's create a function here,
在这里创建一个函数
and we will call it, getMetricMetaInfo.
称为 getMetricMetaInfo
And what this is going to do is we're going to have an object here,
我们将在这里添加一个对象
and this object is going to have five properties which
该对象将具有五个属性
correlate with the specific metrics that we're tracking.
对应的是我们将跟踪的特定指标
So we'll have run, bike,
因此包括 run bike
swim, sleep, as well as eat.
swim sleep 以及 eat
And what these objects are going to contain is they're going to contain
这些对象将包含
any information that's going to help us build the UI for our specific form.
将帮助我们构建具体表格 UI 的所有信息
So for example, here there is specific things about run that we need to know.
例如 对于跑步 我们需要知道这些信息
We need to know the display name,
需要知道 displayName
which is just going to be 'Run'.
直接设为 'Run'
The max miles you can run in a day we'll just say, 50.
一天能跑的最远路程设为 50（英里）
Unit, which we will say is going to be 'miles' the step.
单位 设为 'miles'（英里）
So when we have our form when the user clicks on the button,
step 当我们创建表格 用户点击按钮后
how much we're going to increment this specific count.
我们将按多大的步长递增该计数
That will just be set to 1.
设为 1
Type, we're going to say 'steppers'.
type 设为 'steppers'
So in our UI for the form, if you remember,
在表格 UI 中
there are buttons which we are calling,
有按钮 称为步进器
steppers, and then there's also a slider,
还有滑块
which we will use for sleeping and eating.
将用于睡眠和饮食
And then the last one,
最后
we're going to say, getIcon.
输入 getIcon
And so this is going to do is whenever we invoke the getIcon method here,
每当我们调用这里的 getIcon 方法
what we want to get back is the icon for this specific metric.
我们想要获取这个特定指标的图标
So what we need to do is at the top,
转到顶部
let's go ahead and import a few things.
导入一些内容
We will import 'react' because we're going to be using JSX.
我们将导入 'react' 因为我们将使用 JSX
We will import 'View' from react-native,
将从 react-native 导入 'View'
and then we are going to import a few different icons here from '@expo/vector-icons'.
然后将从 '@expo/vector-icons' 导入一些不同的图标
And there are three different ones we want,
我们需要三种不同的图标
we want the, FontAwesome.
我们想要 FontAwesome
We also want, MaterialIcons.
还想要 MaterialIcons
And then lastly, MaterialCommunityIcons.
最后是 MaterialCommunityIcons
And then we will also import,
我们还将
'white' from our colors file.
从 colors 文件导入 'white'
So now, inside of getIcon,
现在 在 getIcon 中
what we want to do is we want to return a View.
我们想要返回一个 View
We're eventually going to style these, but not right now.
我们最终会设定样式 暂时先不管样式
And then inside of here,
然后在这里面
we are going to use the MaterialIcons.
将使用 MaterialIcons
Name is going to be, 'directions-run'.
名称设为 'directions-run'
Color, it's eventually going to be white, but right now,
color 最终会是白色
let's just go ahead and we'll say,
但暂时设为 'black'
'black' so that we can see it.
这样我们能看见
And then we'll say the size is going to be 35.
size 设为 35
And now what we need to do is we need to do this for every single metric.
我们需要为每个指标都进行这些设置
So what I'm going to do is just copy and paste here,
复制粘贴到这里
and then we will modify them afterwards.
后面会修改的
So 'Bike', displayName is going to be 'Bike'.
对于 bike displayName 将为 'Bike'
Max is going to be 100.
max 将为 100
Step is still 1, 'steppers',
step 依然为 1 'steppers'
and then instead of MaterialIcons,
这里不再使用 MaterialIcons
we are going to use 'MaterialCommunityIcons".
而是 MaterialCommunityIcons
The name of this icon is going to be 'bike',
该图标的名称将为 'bike'
then we will keep it black for now.
暂时为黑色
Swim is going to be very similar.
swim 将非常相似
Max is going to be 9900 because our unit here is going to be in meters.
max 将设为 9900 因为这里的 unit 将是 meters
Step is going to be one 100.
step 将设为 100
And then down here, what we're going to do is we will use the MaterialCommunityIcons,
在这里 我们将使用 MaterialCommunityIcons
but the name of this is now going to be 'swim'.
但是名称将为 'swim'
And the last two here,
剩下最后两个指标
we have 'sleep ',
对于 ’sleep'
which again, is going to be similar.
将很相似
The name is going to be 'Sleep'.
名称将为 'Sleep'
Max is obviously 24.
max 明显是 24
Unit is going to be 'hours'.
unit 将为 'hours'
Instead of steppers, this is going to be a 'slider'.
这里不再是 steppers 而是 'slider'
And then, this is where FontAwesome is going to come in.
然后在这里使用 FontAwesome
And we will say the name is going to be 'bed'.
名称将为 'bed'
And again, this is just a icon from FontAwesome.
这是一个来自 FontAwesome 的图标
And then lastly, we have 'eat' with display name of 'Eat'.
最后对于 'eat' displayName 为 'Eat'
A max of 10 because this is going to be from 1-10.
max 为 10 因为将是 1-10
Unit will be a 'rating', 'slider'.
unit 将为 'rating' 设为 ’slider'
And then lastly, again,
最后
we're going to have MaterialCommunityIcons,
将使用 MaterialCommunityIcons
with the name being 'food'. All right.
名称为 'food'
So now what we have is we have this giant object here that we're calling, info.
现在我们有了这个庞大的对象 称为 info
And then what I want to do is if I invoke getMetricaInfo and I don't pass an argument,
如果我调用 getMetricaInfo 并且不传入参数
then what I want to do is just return this whole object.
直接返回整个对象
But if I do pass it, an argument,
但是如果我传入一个参数
specifically the metric, what I want to do is return just that metric.
具体而言是 metric 我想返回该 metric
And on here, what we're going to do is we will say if
在这里进行设置
metric is undefined or if its type is undefined,
如果 metric 未定义 或其类型未定义
then what we want to return is just the info object.
然后我们直接返回 info 对象
And if it isn't,
如果不是这种情况
then let's go ahead and return info at that specific metric.
则返回该指标的信息